Philip Singer Papers
Philip Singer Papers
- Films
  - The Last Mattanza
    - Recordings, contains both English and Italian versions of film
      - L'Ultima Tonnara/Mattanza, Selects for Dr. Singer, singer_p_0066; National Geographic label on side of tape, possible film edit for National Geographic; VHS; running time 60:00 (Box 30)
      - L'Ultima Tonnara Mattanza, singer_p_1562; English edit; DVD; running time 113:00 (Box 43)
  - Life and Death of an Alternative Healer: Wanita Windwalker, Shaman, Psychic
    - Review, 2000 (Box 1)
  - La Malinche
    - "La Malinche in Mexico Literature: From History to Myth," Sandra Messinger Cypress, 1991 (Box 7)
    - Script, undated (Box 7)
  - Medicine Woman and Medicine Man: Traditional Holistic Medicine in Middle America
    - Review, 1987 (Box 2)
    - Recordings
      - Medicine Woman and Medicine Man: Traditional Holistic Medicine in Middle America, singer_p_1188; DVD; running time 38:00 (Oversize 5)
  - Motoyama
    - Articles in English, 1979-1983 (Box 7)
    - Tapes 1-6, 1984 (Box 7)
  - Museum Security Guards as Art Connisseurs; Detroit Institute of Arts
    - Film review, Oakland Journal, 2000 (Box 7)
    - Recordings
      - Museum Security Guards as Art Connoisseurs; Detroit Institute of Arts, singer_p_1232; Detroit Institute of Arts; DVD; running time 85:00 (Oversize 6)
      - Museum Security Guards as Art Connoisseurs; Detroit Institute of Arts, singer_p_0072; VHS; running time 85:00 (Box 30)
      - Museum Security Guards as Art Connoisseurs Detroit Institute of Arts, singer_p_0073; VHS; running time 85:00 (Box 30)
  - Nigeria Series 1-7
    - Advertising sheet, undated (Box 7)
  - One of The Mad Ones
    - Clippings, 1988 (Box 7)
    - Conference presentation, 2012 (Box 7)
    - Correspondence, 1986-1991 (Box 7)
    - Interview with "Mad Man", 1969-1974; mob therapy group interview (Box 7)
    - Mad in America interview, 2014 (Box 8)
    - Mental illness, 1974-1988 (Box 8)
    - Review, 2011 (Box 2)
    - Schizophrenia and Dr. DeSole, 1989-1991 (Box 8)
    - Third World Conference, 2012 (Box 23)
    - Recordings, multiple copies of DVDs were kept because content could not be verified
      - One of the Mad Ones, singer_p_0938; DVD; running time 99:00 (Oversize 4)
      - One of the Mad Ones (Enhanced), singer_p_0928; DVD; running time 99:00 (Oversize 4)
      - One of the Mad Ones (Enhanced), singer_p_0929; DVD; running time 99:00 (Oversize 4)
      - One of the Mad Ones (Enhanced), singer_p_0930; DVD; running time 99:00 (Oversize 4)
      - One of the Mad Ones (Enhanced), singer_p_0931; DVD; running time 99:00 (Oversize 4)
      - One of the Mad Ones (Enhanced), singer_p_0932; DVD; running time 99:00 (Oversize 4)
      - One of the Mad Ones (Subtitled), singer_p_0926; DVD; running time 99:00 (Oversize 4)
      - One of the Mad Ones (Subtitled), singer_p_0927; DVD; running time 99:00 (Oversize 4)
      - One of the Mad Ones, singer_p_0919; DVD; running time 99:00 (Oversize 4)
      - One of the Mad Ones, singer_p_0933; DVD; running time 93:00 (Oversize 4)
      - One of the Mad Ones, singer_p_0920; DVD; running time 99:00 (Oversize 4)
      - One of the Mad Ones, singer_p_0934; DVD; running time 93:00 (Oversize 4)
      - One of the Mad Ones, singer_p_0935; DVD; running time 93:00 (Oversize 4)
      - One of the Mad Ones, singer_p_0936; DVD; running time 93:00 (Oversize 4)
      - One of the Mad Ones, V. 1 (No Subtitles), singer_p_0937; DVD; running time 93:00 (Oversize 4)
      - One of the Mad Ones, V. 2 [Copy 1], singer_p_0921; DVD; running time 93:00 (Oversize 4)
      - One of the Mad Ones, V. 2 [Copy 2], singer_p_0922; DVD; running time 93:00 (Oversize 4)
      - One of the Mad Ones, V. 3 [Copy 1], singer_p_0923; DVD; running time 99:00 (Oversize 4)
      - One of the Mad Ones, V. 3 [Copy 2], singer_p_0924; DVD; running time 99:00 (Oversize 4)
      - One of the Mad Ones, V. 4, singer_p_0925; DVD; running time 99:00 (Oversize 4)
      - One of the Mad Ones, v.4, singer_p_1178; DVD; running time 99:00 (Oversize 5)
      - One of the Mad Ones, v.4, singer_p_1179; DVD; running time 99:00 (Oversize 5)
      - One of the Mad Ones, v.4, singer_p_1180; subtitled; DVD; running time 99:00 (Oversize 5)
  - Pain Control: Alternative Therapies
    - Recordings
      - Pain Control: Alternative Therapies, singer_p_0910; label on DVD reads, "England, Middle America, Israel"; DVD; running time 93:00 (Oversize 4)
      - Pain Control: Alternative Therapies, singer_p_0911; label on DVD reads, "England, Middle America, Israel"; DVD; running time 93:00 (Oversize 4)
      - Pain Control: Alternative Therapies, singer_p_0912; label on DVD reads, "England, Middle America, Israel"; DVD; running time 93:00 (Oversize 4)
      - Pain Control: Alternative Therapies Part I and II, singer_p_0074; includes Philip Singer business card; VHS; running time 88:00 (Box 30)
      - Pain Control: Alternative Therapies Part I and II, singer_p_0075; includes Philip Singer business card; VHS; running time 88:00 (Box 30)
      - Pain Control: Alternative Therapies, Part I, singer_p_0165; VHS; running time 60:00 (Box 38)
      - Pain Control: Alternative Therapies, Part II, singer_p_0166; VHS; running time 34:00 (Box 38)
  - Participant Observation or Clinical Anthropology: Is This Ethnomedicine? Ego Trip? Ethical?
    - Recordings
      - Participant Observation or Clinical Anthropology: Is This Ethnomedicine? Ego Trip? Ethical?, singer_p_1023; DVD; running time 60:00 (Oversize 4)
      - Participant Observation or Clinical Anthropology: Is This Ethnomedicine? Ego Trip? Ethical?, singer_p_1024; DVD; running time 60:00 (Oversize 4)
      - Participant Observation or Clinical Anthropology: Is This Ethnomedicine? Ego Trip? Ethical?, singer_p_1025; DVD; running time 60:00 (Oversize 4)
      - Participant Observation or Clinical Anthropology: Is This Ethnomedicine? Ego Trip? Ethical?, singer_p_1026; DVD; running time 60:00 (Oversize 4)
      - Participant Observation or Clinical Anthropology: Is This Ethnomedicine? Ego Trip? Ethical?, singer_p_1229; DVD; running time 60:00 (Oversize 6)
  - Persistent Vegetative State
    - Recordings
      - Persistent Vegetative State, singer_p_1218; label on case reads, "What is life? When is death? What is the law?"; DVD; running time 56:55 (Oversize 6)
      - Persistent Vegetative State, singer_p_1292; text on disc reads, "Intro - P[hilip] S[inger], Rosebush interview, film Irreversible Coma"; DVD; running time 31:00 (Oversize 6)
      - Persistent Vegetative State: What is Life? When is Death? What is the Law?, singer_p_1042; DVD; running time 56:00 (Oversize 5)
      - Persistent Vegetative State: What is Life? When is Death? What is the Law?, singer_p_1043; DVD; running time 56:00 (Oversize 5)
      - Persistent Vegetative State: What is Life? When is Death? What is the Law?, singer_p_1044; DVD; running time 56:00 (Oversize 5)
      - Persistent Vegetative State: What is Life? When is Death? What is the Law?, singer_p_1433; label on case reads, "30:00 of 56:00"; DVD; running time 30:00 (Box 55)
      - We Are All Natives: Persistent Vegetative State, singer_p_0107; VHS; running time 30:00 (Box 33)
  - Psychiatric Commitment: A Documentary
    - Review, 1991-1992 (Box 2)
    - Recordings
      - Psychiatric Commitment, singer_p_1081; DVD; running time 80:00 (Oversize 5)
      - Psychiatric Commitment: A Documentary, singer_p_0077; VHS; running time 80:00 (Box 31)
      - Psychiatric Commitment: A Documentary, singer_p_0078; VHS; running time 80:00 (Box 31)
      - Psychiatric Commitment: A Documentary, singer_p_0079; VHS; running time 80:00 (Box 31)
  - Psychic Surgery: A Case of Shamanic Sleight-of-Hand
    - Review, 1988 (Box 2)
  - The Public Health Physician Making Medicine in Mexico
    - Recordings
      - The Public Health Physician Making Medicine in Mexico [Copy 1], singer_p_0082; VHS; running time 45:00 (Box 31)
      - The Public Health Physician Making Medicine in Mexico [Copy 2], singer_p_0083; VHS; running time 45:00 (Box 31)
      - The Public Health Physician Making Medicine in Mexico [Copy 1], singer_p_1367; DVD; running time 60:00 (Box 54)
      - The Public Health Physician Making Medicine in Mexico [Copy 2], singer_p_1368; DVD; running time 60:00 (Box 54)
  - Sicilian Women Orgasm – Vaginal or Clitoral?
    - Recordings
      - Sicilian Women [Orgasm -- Vaginal or Clitoral?], singer_p_0960; with Laura Olvsy; DVD; running time 56:00 (Oversize 4)
      - Sicilian Women [Orgasm -- Vaginal or Clitoral?], singer_p_0961; with Anna Luisa and Orella XX; DVD; running time 65:00 (Oversize 4)
      - Sicilian Women [Orgasm -- Vaginal or Clitoral?], singer_p_0962; with Trapani; DVD; running time 56:00 (Oversize 4)
      - Sicilian Women [Orgasm -- Vaginal or Clitoral?], singer_p_0963; with Edicoli, Madonna streets; DVD; running time 56:00 (Oversize 4)
      - Sicilian Women [Orgasm -- Vaginal or Clitoral?], singer_p_0964; with Archidonna; DVD; running time 32:00 (Oversize 4)
      - Sicilian Women [Orgasm -- Vaginal or Clitoral?], singer_p_0965; two interviews; DVD; running time 60:00 (Oversize 4)
      - Sicilian Women [Orgasm -- Vaginal or Clitoral?], singer_p_0966; label on disc reads, "Alcamo 1 and 2"; DVD; running time 80:00 (Oversize 4)
      - Sicilian Women [Orgasm -- Vaginal or Clitoral?], singer_p_0967; with Marian; DVD; running time 70:00 (Oversize 4)
      - Sicilian Women [Orgasm -- Vaginal or Clitoral?], singer_p_0968; label on disc reads, "Barbara cut-aways, Alessandra, Maria Pina"; DVD; running time 60:00 (Oversize 4)
      - Sicilian Women [Orgasm -- Vaginal or Clitoral?], singer_p_0969; with Monica Teatro Massimo; DVD; running time 46:00 (Oversize 4)
      - Sicilian Women [Orgasm -- Vaginal or Clitoral?], singer_p_0970; with Maria; DVD; running time 36:00 (Oversize 4)
      - Sicilian Women [Orgasm -- Vaginal or Clitoral?], singer_p_1067; with Trapani; DVD; running time 56:00 (Oversize 5)
      - Sicilian Women [Orgasm -- Vaginal or Clitoral?], singer_p_1068; with Francesca, Paula, and Alessih - students; DVD; running time 50:00 (Oversize 5)
      - Sicilian Women [Orgasm -- Vaginal or Clitoral?], singer_p_1069; with Decmo, M.D.; DVD; running time 40:00 (Oversize 5)
      - Sicilian Women [Orgasm -- Vaginal or Clitoral?], singer_p_1070; with Rafaella/Antonella; DVD; running time 40:00 (Oversize 5)
      - Sicilian Women [Orgasm -- Vaginal or Clitoral?], singer_p_1071; with older women; DVD; running time 56:00 (Oversize 5)
      - Sicilian Women Orgasm -- Vaginal or Clitoral?, singer_p_0872; DVD; running time 110:00 (Oversize 4)
      - Sicilian Women Orgasm -- Vaginal or Clitoral?, singer_p_0873; DVD; running time 110:00 (Oversize 4)
      - Sicilian Women Orgasm -- Vaginal or Clitoral?, singer_p_0874; DVD; running time 110:00 (Oversize 4)
      - Sicilian Women Orgasm -- Vaginal or Clitoral?, singer_p_0904; DVD; running time 110:00 (Oversize 4)
      - Sicilian Women Orgasm -- Vaginal or Clitoral?, singer_p_0905; DVD; running time 110:00 (Oversize 4)
      - Sicilian Women Orgasm -- Vaginal or Clitoral? Rosalia, MD #2, singer_p_0869; DVD; running time 20:00 (Oversize 4)
      - Sicilian Women Orgasm -- Vaginal or Clitoral? Rosalia, MD #2, singer_p_0870; DVD; running time 20:00 (Oversize 4)
      - Sicilian Women Orgasm -- Vaginal or Clitoral? Rosalia, MD #2, singer_p_0871; DVD; running time 20:00 (Oversize 4)
      - Sicilian Women Orgasm -- Vaginal or Clitoral? Rosalia, MD #2, singer_p_0956; DVD; running time 20:00 (Oversize 4)
      - Sicilian Women Orgasm -- Vaginal or Clitoral? Sicilian Psychiatrists, singer_p_0876; DVD; running time 98:00 (Oversize 4)
      - Sicilian Women Orgasm -- Vaginal or Clitoral? Sicilian Psychiatrists #4, singer_p_0877; DVD; running time 98:00 (Oversize 4)
      - Sicilian Women Orgasm -- Vaginal or Clitoral? Sicilian Psychiatrists #4, singer_p_0878; DVD; running time 98:00 (Oversize 4)
      - Sicilian Women Orgasm -- Vaginal or Clitoral? Sicilian Psychiatrists #4, singer_p_0879; DVD; running time 98:00 (Oversize 4)
      - Sicilian Women Orgasm -- Vaginal or Clitoral? Sicilian Psychiatrists #4, singer_p_0880; DVD; running time 98:00 (Oversize 4)
      - Sicilian Women Orgasm -- Vaginal or Clitoral? Vagina Monologues Interviews #3, singer_p_0867; DVD; running time 74:00 (Oversize 4)
      - Sicilian Women Orgasm -- Vaginal or Clitoral? Vagina Monologues Interviews #3, singer_p_0868; DVD; running time 74:00 (Oversize 4)
      - Sicilian Women Orgasm -- Vaginal or Clitoral? Vagina Monologues Interviews #3, singer_p_0875; DVD; running time 74:00 (Oversize 4)
      - Sicilian Women Orgasm -- Vaginal or Clitoral? Vagina Monologues Interviews #3, singer_p_0957; DVD; running time 74:00 (Oversize 4)
      - Sicilian Women Orgasm -- Vaginal or Clitoral? Vagina Monologues Interviews #3, singer_p_0958; DVD; running time 74:00 (Oversize 4)
      - Sicilian Women Orgasm -- Vaginal or Clitoral? Vagina Monologues Interviews #3, singer_p_0959; DVD; running time 74:00 (Oversize 4)
      - Sicilian Women: Orgasm -- Vaginal or Clitoral?, singer_p_1297; DVD; running time 110:00 (Box 52)
      - [Sicilian] #1, raw footage for presumably Sicilian Women: Orgasm -- Vaginal or Clitoral, description on tape reads, "Sicilian Laura Giusy"; singer_p_0321; MiniDV; running time 60:00 (Box 45)
      - [Sicilian] #2, 2001; singer_p_0322; raw footage for presumably Sicilian Women: Orgasm -- Vaginal or Clitoral, description on tape reads, "Edicoli Palormo 5/10/01"; MiniDV; running time 60:00 (Box 45)
      - [Sicilian] #3 & 4, 2001; singer_p_0324; raw footage for presumably Sicilian Women: Orgasm -- Vaginal or Clitoral, description on tape reads, "Palermo interview by Tony, Anna, Esmeralda"; MiniDV; running time 60:00 (Box 45)
      - [Sicilian] #4, 2001; raw footage for presumably Sicilian Women: Orgasm -- Vaginal or Clitoral, description on tape reads, "Monica Antonorla, Dr. Sandra 4/26/2001"; singer_p_0325; MiniDV; running time 60:00 (Box 45)
      - [Sicilian] #6, 2001; raw footage for presumably Sicilian Women: Orgasm -- Vaginal or Clitoral, description on tape reads, "Palermo, Francesca, Paula, Alessea - Giussy"; singer_p_0326; MiniDV; running time 50:00 (Box 45)
      - [Sicilian] #7, 2001; raw footage for presumably Sicilian Women: Orgasm -- Vaginal or Clitoral, description on tape reads, "Serena, Palermo, Tony interviews, 3/15/2001"; singer_p_0327; MiniDV; running time 60:00 (Box 45)
      - [Sicilian] #8, 2001; raw footage for presumably Sicilian Women: Orgasm -- Vaginal or Clitoral, description on tape reads, "Maria Giouanna, [illegible] David chat only 4/26"; singer_p_0328; MiniDV; running time 60:00 (Box 45)
      - [Sicilian] #9, 2001; singer_p_0329; raw footage for presumably Sicilian Women: Orgasm -- Vaginal or Clitoral, description on tape reads, "Georgia Sp. Palli, M.D. Palermo 3/17"; MiniDV; running time 60:00 (Box 45)
      - [Sicilian] #10, 2001; singer_p_0330; raw footage for presumably Sicilian Women: Orgasm -- Vaginal or Clitoral, description on tape reads, "Alessandra, Maria Pena 3/23"; MiniDV; running time 60:00 (Box 45)
      - [Sicilian] #10, Raffele Britella, 2001; singer_p_0331; raw footage for presumably Sicilian Women: Orgasm -- Vaginal or Clitoral, description on tape reads, "Britella Antonella"; MiniDV; running time 60:00 (Box 45)
      - [Sicilian] #12, 2001; singer_p_0332; raw footage for presumably Sicilian Women: Orgasm -- Vaginal or Clitoral, description on tape reads, "Monica Massimo Thetre"; MiniDV; running time 60:00 (Box 45)
      - [Sicilian] #13, 2001; singer_p_0333; raw footage for presumably Sicilian Women: Orgasm -- Vaginal or Clitoral, description on tape reads, "Edicoli Palermo"; MiniDV; running time 60:00 (Box 45)
      - [Sicilian] #13 Elizabeth Tropani, 2001; singer_p_0334; raw footage for presumably Sicilian Women: Orgasm -- Vaginal or Clitoral, description on tape reads, "Elizabeth Tropani, Nanda - Tropani"; MiniDV; running time 60:00 (Box 45)
      - [Sicilian] #14, 2001; raw footage for presumably Sicilian Women: Orgasm -- Vaginal or Clitoral, description on tape reads, "Anna - Traponi, Elizabeth - Traponi"; singer_p_0335; MiniDV; running time 60:00 (Box 45)
      - [Sicilian] #16, 2001; raw footage for presumably Sicilian Women: Orgasm -- Vaginal or Clitoral, description on tape reads, "Trapani, Speranza, Margarita, Janna 3/27/01"; singer_p_0336; MiniDV; running time 60:00 (Box 45)
      - [Sicilian] #17, 2001; raw footage for presumably Sicilian Women: Orgasm -- Vaginal or Clitoral, description on tape reads, "Anna Trapani, Caterina"; singer_p_0337; MiniDV; running time 60:00 (Box 45)
      - [Sicilian] #18, 2001; singer_p_0338; raw footage for presumably Sicilian Women: Orgasm -- Vaginal or Clitoral, description on tape reads, "Sicilian [illegible], older women, Francesca, Marigria"; MiniDV; running time 60:00 (Box 45)
      - [Sicilian] #20, 2001; singer_p_0339; raw footage for presumably Sicilian Women: Orgasm -- Vaginal or Clitoral, description on tape reads, "Orella - Palommo"; MiniDV; running time 60:00 (Box 45)
      - [Sicilian] #21, 2001; singer_p_0340; raw footage for presumably Sicilian Women: Orgasm -- Vaginal or Clitoral, description on tape reads, "Tony re: joint"; MiniDV; running time 60:00 (Box 45)
      - [Sicilian] #22, 2001; singer_p_0341; raw footage for presumably Sicilian Women: Orgasm -- Vaginal or Clitoral, description on tape reads, "Vagina Monologue - Trapani"; MiniDV; running time 60:00 (Box 45)
      - [Sicilian] #23, 2001; singer_p_0342; raw footage for presumably Sicilian Women: Orgasm -- Vaginal or Clitoral, description on tape reads, "Vagina Monologue - Trapani"; MiniDV; running time 60:00 (Box 45)
      - [Sicilian] #24, 2001; raw footage for presumably Sicilian Women: Orgasm -- Vaginal or Clitoral, description on tape reads, "Dr. Decimo - Alcamo"; singer_p_0343; MiniDV; running time 60:00 (Box 45)
      - [Sicilian] #26, 2001; singer_p_0344; raw footage for presumably Sicilian Women: Orgasm -- Vaginal or Clitoral, description on tape reads, "Marina Polizzi, Palermo, Markinno Santoro"; MiniDV; running time 60:00 (Box 45)
      - [Sicilian] #27, 2001; raw footage for presumably Sicilian Women: Orgasm -- Vaginal or Clitoral, description on tape reads, "Musotto, Agnello, [illegible]"; singer_p_0345; MiniDV; running time 60:00 (Box 45)
      - [Sicilian] Alcamo (1 of 2), 2001; singer_p_0348; note on tape reads, "Sent to Tony for Marisa," raw footage for presumably Sicilian Women: Orgasm -- Vaginal or Clitoral; MiniDV; running time 60:00 (Box 45)
      - [Sicilian] Alcamo #2, 2001; singer_p_0323; raw footage for presumably Sicilian Women: Orgasm -- Vaginal or Clitoral; MiniDV; running time 60:00 (Box 45)
      - [Sicilian] Archdonna Palermo, 2001; singer_p_0346; raw footage for presumably Sicilian Women: Orgasm -- Vaginal or Clitoral; MiniDV; running time 31:00 (Box 45)
      - [Sicilian] Italia, 2000; singer_p_0352; raw footage for presumably Sicilian Women: Orgasm -- Vaginal or Clitoral; MiniDV; running time 60:00 (Box 45)
      - [Sicilian] Men's Hair Stylist, Palermo (cut aways), 2001; singer_p_0351; note on tape reads, "DVD recorded 4/6/06," raw footage for presumably Sicilian Women: Orgasm -- Vaginal or Clitoral; MiniDV; running time 60:00 (Box 45)
      - [Sicilian] Pozzuole Marisso, 2001; singer_p_0347; note on tape reads, "Sent to Tony for Marisa," raw footage for presumably Sicilian Women: Orgasm -- Vaginal or Clitoral; MiniDV; running time 60:00 (Box 45)
      - [Sicilian] Rosalia, M.D., Palermo responds to Decimo, MD, 2001; singer_p_0350; note on tape reads, "DVD recorded 4/6/06," raw footage for presumably Sicilian Women: Orgasm -- Vaginal or Clitoral; MiniDV; running time 60:00 (Box 45)
      - [Sicilian] The Kiss Palermo, 2001; singer_p_0349; note on tape reads, "Sent to Tony for Marisa," raw footage for presumably Sicilian Women: Orgasm -- Vaginal or Clitoral; MiniDV; running time 60:00 (Box 45)
  - The 3-Day Kali Mai in Guyana: Goddess Worship
    - Recordings
      - The 3-Day Kali Mai in Guyana: Goddess Worship, singer_p_0975; DVD; running time 153:00 (Oversize 4)
      - The 3-Day Kali Mai in Guyana: Goddess Worship (part 1 of 2), singer_p_0976; DVD; running time 120:00 (Oversize 4)
  - The 3-Day Kali Mai Puja
    - Recordings
      - The 3-Day Kali Mai Puja: Death of Pandit Jamsie Guyana, singer_p_0971; DVD; running time 153:00 (Oversize 4)
      - The 3-Day Kali Mai Puja: Death of Pandit Jamsie Guyana, singer_p_0972; DVD; running time 153:00 (Oversize 4)
      - The 3-Day Kali Mai Puja: Death of Pandit Jamsie Guyana, singer_p_0973; DVD; running time 153:00 (Oversize 4)
      - The 3-Day Kali Mai Puja: Death of Pandit Jamsie Guyana, singer_p_0974; DVD; running time 153:00 (Oversize 4)
      - The 3-Day Kali Mai Puja: First Day in Cargum, singer_p_0982; DVD; running time 47:00 (Oversize 4)
  - Traditional Healing Ecuador: Evil Wind Evil Air
    - Recordings
      - Traditional Healing Ecuador: "Evil Wind Evil Air" (Subtitles), singer_p_1045; DVD; running time 21:00 (Oversize 5)
      - Traditional Healing Ecuador: "Evil Wind Evil Air" (Subtitles), singer_p_1046; DVD; running time 21:00 (Oversize 5)
      - Traditional Healing Ecuador: "Evil Wind Evil Air" (Subtitles), singer_p_1047; DVD; running time 21:00 (Oversize 5)
      - Traditional Healing Ecuador: "Evil Wind Evil Air" (Subtitles), singer_p_1048; DVD; running time 21:00 (Box 51)
  - Traditional Healing Nigeria
    - Recordings
      - Traditional Healing Nigeria #1: The Urban Encounter Traditionalism and Allopathy, singer_p_1123; DVD; running time 26:00 (Oversize 5)
      - Traditional Healing Nigeria #1: The Urban Encounter Traditionalism and Allopathy, singer_p_1127; DVD; running time 26:00 (Oversize 5)
      - Traditional Healing Nigeria #2: An Urban Traditional G P, singer_p_1124; DVD; running time 14:00 (Oversize 5)
      - Traditional Healing Nigeria #2: An Urban Traditional G P, singer_p_1129; DVD; running time 14:00 (Oversize 5)
      - Traditional Healing Nigeria #2: An Urban Traditional G P, OB-GYN, singer_p_1125; DVD; running time 14:00 (Oversize 5)
      - Traditional Healing Nigeria #3: An Urban Traditional Specialist OB-GYN, singer_p_1130; DVD; running time 13:00 (Oversize 5)
      - Traditional Healing Nigeria #3: An Urban Traditional Specialist OB-GYN, singer_p_1131; DVD; running time 13:00 (Oversize 5)
      - Traditional Healing Nigeria #4: Urban Traditional Specialist Mental Illness, singer_p_1132; DVD; running time 15:00 (Oversize 5)
      - Traditional Healing Nigeria #4: Urban Traditional Specialist Mental Illness, singer_p_1133; DVD; running time 15:00 (Oversize 5)
      - Traditional Healing Nigeria #5: Traditional Specialist IFA Divination Diagnosis, singer_p_1126; DVD; running time 11:00 (Oversize 5)
      - Traditional Healing Nigeria #5: Traditional Specialist IFA Divination Diagnosis, singer_p_1134; DVD; running time 11:00 (Oversize 5)
      - Traditional Healing Nigeria #6: Traditional Rural Specialist Bonemender, singer_p_1135; DVD; running time 09:00 (Oversize 5)
      - Traditional Healing Nigeria #6: Traditional Rural Specialist Bonemender, singer_p_1136; DVD; running time 09:00 (Oversize 5)
      - Traditional Healing Nigeria #7: No More Secrets Initiation and Change, singer_p_1137; DVD; running time 24:00 (Oversize 5)
      - Traditional Healing Nigeria #7: No More Secrets Initiation and Change, singer_p_1138; DVD; running time 24:00 (Oversize 5)
      - Traditional Healing Nigeria Series: An Urban Specialist, singer_p_1121; sympathetic magic; DVD; running time 14:00 (Oversize 5)
      - Traditional Healing Nigeria Series: An Urban Specialist, singer_p_1128; sympathetic magic; DVD; running time 14:00 (Oversize 5)
  - Traditional Healing Productions, Singer's film production company
    - Advertisement sheets, 1991 (Box 2)
    - Advertisement sheets, 1992-1993 (Box 8)
    - Legal suit, 1999 (Box 8)
    - Newspaper clippings, 1980-1996 (Box 8)